Nobita's Wife-To-Be
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
The baby in this photo has grown this big already!
Time sure flies.
Now he's a good student.
Happy Birthday! Cheers!
Thanks!
Soon he will graduate to become Junior High student.
Then, Senior High, then College.
Only if he can manage to, that is.
Shut up!
After graduating from college, he will be an refined adult...
Then he will get married...
Wife!
But only if someone marries you, that is.
Shut up! That's mean of you!
But I am telling the truth!
Stop, Doraemon!
Stop it!
No one is going to marry you!
Hey, stop!
Stop it!
But... I'm kind of concerned.
Why?!
What if I can't marry a girl?
Are you seriously worried?
Then in that case, why don't we go, see your future by ourselves?
See what?
Using the Time Machine to go to the future to see my Wife-To-Be?
Yes, my Wife-To-Be!
I'm so shy!
Forget it then!
No, I wanna see.
Do you wanna see or not?
Here we are!
Toilet?
This place is full of toilets.
The site where my house had once stood, has become a public toilet now.
The streets are totally different!
Ah, Mr. Nobi's house that once stood there!
It's been 10 years since they moved to the apartment around the corner.
It's a park now!
That's the mansion!
#68, the 12th floor. I am so thrilled to see my Wife.
I am very nervous. I wonder who my wife is?
I'm knocking on the door
Wait a sec, Doraemon.
I don't think it's a good idea to see my wife in this way?
Maybe...
I'll just have a peek on her secretly.
Let's use this transparent mirror!
You can see through things using this.
I saw only from the behind.
Oh no!
I don't wanna marry her!
But what can I do?
What is Ms. Nobi doing?
This can't be true!
My future is full of misery.
Caught you! You sure are a naughty boy!
You're...
Ms. Minamoto Shizuka, 25 years in the future?
Don't talk to your mother like that!
Now, you're coming with me.
Sunetaro's mum is here.
Be sure to apologize to her!
Nobisuke always give my Sunetaro a hard time.
I admit that he's very mischievous.
Please discipline your boy.
I'm truly sorry.
Nobisuke looks just like me!
That means, I'm his father!
His mum is Shizuka-chan!
Yay!
So it's you!
How rude of you to talk like that with your mother?
Your dad is a gentleman, but from whom on earth do you take after?
Ouch, it hurts!
I'm home!
Oh, that's my son, Nobisuke!
Who the hell are you? Why are you here?
Hey Nobisuke, be a good boy and properly do your studies!
Stop it!
How dare you do this to your father?!
You must be an alien!
Coming here to occupy my house!
Help!
Stop it, aliens!
Hold it right there!
Let's go home using the Time Machine!
Come on out!
Open the door!
He is too mean!
He is too energetic!
Where'd have you been, all this time? Shizuka-chan is here to wish you.
Happy birthday, Nobita-kun!
Thanks!
Why are you being shy all of a sudden? You sure are a weird kid!